Stock markets typically remain open for a finite number of hours every day,
股市通常在每天的特定时段内开市
say 9:30 AM to 4:00 PM.
例如从上午 9:30 到下午 4:00
This is when the majority of the transactions take place.
大部分交易都出现在这个时段
Why you ask?
为何呢？
Well, traders and exchange operators are humans just like you and me.
交易者和交易操作员也是人 和你我一样
They need to go back to their families,
他们需要陪伴家人 需要睡觉
sleep, and live a life.
并且有自己的生活
Okay, there is another reason.
还有一个原因
With the growing popularity of algorithmic trading,
随着算法交易越来越受欢迎
a large portion of transactions today are being carried out by automated systems.
如今有很大一部分交易都是由自动化系统执行的
They can be much more responsive to market conditions than humans,
他们对市场条件的响应速度比人类要快
and result in a sharp increase or decrease in
导致股价在很短时间内
stock prices over a very short period of time.
就出现暴涨和暴跌
If left unchecked, this can result in things spiraling out of control.
如果不控制这些情况 可能会导致股市失控
Closing market operations at a regular time every day provides
每天定期收盘可以形成人为屏障
an artificial barrier that can limit the damage such events can cause.
并限制此类事件带来的损害
This also give stock market regulators some time to
此外 使股市调节者有时间
analyze the situation and implement control measures.
分析行情并落实控制措施
Now, some exchanges do allow for pre-market and post-market trading.
某些交易所允许盘前交易和盘后交易
Typically 4:00 AM to 9:30 AM for pre-market,
盘前交易通常是从凌晨 4:00 到上午 9:30
and 4:00 PM to 8:00 PM post-market.
盘后交易是从下午 4:00 到晚上 8:00
However, not many traders participate in the session.
但是 并没有多少交易者在这些时段交易
So, trading volume is typically low.
所以成交量很低
Either way, the takeaway from this is that
总之
stock markets close operations at a certain time every day,
股市在每天的特定时间会关闭
and they typically remain closed over weekends and holidays.
并且一般在周末和节假日也会关闭
As a result, when you look at stock data,
所以 当你观察股票数据时会发现
you'll notice these gaps or discontinuities during periods when the markets are closed.
当股市关闭时 会出现这些缺口或不连续性
Depending on your analysis,
这些缺口可能会对你的结论有影响
this may or may not have an impact on the conclusions you draw.
取决于你的分析角度
For instance, if you treat market data as a simple sequence of observations and ignore
例如 如果你将市场数据当做一系列的观察值
the timestamps as if the market's just smoothly
并忽略时间戳 就好像市场
continue from one end of day to the next opening bell,
从一天收盘平稳过渡到第二天开盘
then these gaps are not as significant.
那么这些缺口不重要
But, if you compute a metric that involves time like the number of transactions per hour,
但是如果计算与时间有关的指标 例如每小时的交易量
then ignoring these gaps can give you inaccurate results.
那么忽略这些缺口会导致结果不准确
The discontinuities can produce spikes or unusual flats in calculated values,
不连续性会导致计算的值出现峰值或不正常的平缓区间
or just outright wrong information.
或者直接提供错误的信息
So, you need to be careful when dealing with market data.
所以在处理市场数据时要注意